Find the D in Find Tuning, and hand in the quality of a garment.
If you want to change the quality of the garment, you can do it in the file One Piece and hand in the quality of the camera, or drag it into the 2D or 3D window.
Sometimes in the simulation process, the garment may be deformed.
After improving the quality of the garment, the simulation speed will slow down, so it is not recommended to change the 3D garment after using the function.
On the contrary,
If you want to reduce the quality of the garment, you can review the problems that may occur in the simulation process.
Go to the 3D tool bar and select Reduce the quality of the garment.
A window will appear where you can adjust the quality of the garment.
Click OK to apply the settings.
Activate the simulation and adjust the 3D garment.
If you have trouble using the AI writing take this Morgan is OK.
Again using the PREVENT quality tools, the 3D quality of the garment, simulate again.
Save to continue.
Go to the ProcedureArt tab and choose Show quality.
You can save to your propriation alone without any good results.
Thank you.